ROHITH GODFREY

Audio Engineer | Music Teacher

Mobile: 9445450904

Email: arohithgodfrey@gmail.com

With Diploma in Audio Engineering and Music Production , I specialize in studio recording, sound mixing & mastering, and audio production. I've managed number of studio sessions, ensuring topnotch audio quality. My passion for Audio Engineering , Sound Mixing and Audio post production drives me to constantly innovate and achieve the best sound possible.

EDUCATION

SOUNDTECH MEDIA

2022 - 2023

• QUALIFICATION - Diploma in Sound Engineering and Music Production

ST. XAVIER'S CATHOLIC COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING

QUALIFICATION – BE Electronics and Communication

2018-2022

WORK EXPERIENCE

Audio Engineer

2018 - 2023

RG Records, Nagercoil.

Managed studio recording sessions and post–production sound mixing and Mastering.

- Led recording sessions for Songs and Dubbing Sessions.
- Utilized advanced Logic Pro X, Pro tools, Cubase Elements, Waves, UAD and ozone plugins and softwares.

Music Teacher WhiteHat Junior

2021 - 2023

- 1700+ Hours of experience in teaching.
- Mastery Level Course Completed.
- Trained students for Trinity College London Grade exams.

SKILLS:

- Audio technician & engineer (live & post production)
- Mixing & Mastering
- Digital Audio Workstation (Logic Pro X, Pro Tools, Cubase
- · Sound Design
- Problem Solving

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Completed Piano Grade 8 in Trinity College London.
- Worked & Recorded more than 200 Songs/ Short Film/ Serial.
- · Produced more than 20 Songs.
- Mixed more than 30 songs.
- Regularly attend workshops to stay updated with the latest audio engineering techniques.

STRENGTH

Studio Recording

 Managed several studio sessions, ensuring high-quality audio capture.

Sound Mixing

 Mixed and Mastered tracks for artists, achieving clear and balanced sound.

DECLARATION

I hereby declared that the details mentioned above are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.